ampower.me 2018-10-19

# Ampower Privacy

Ampower IT Pvt Ltd., ("Ampower, Ampowers," "we" or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy and the security of personally identifying information ("Personal Information. This privacy policy explains how we collect, use and disclose information about you when you use our website/mobile website (the "Site or mobile applications (the "Apps") and other online products and services that link to this privacy policy (collectively, the "Service"). By using the Service, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content on, or privacy practices, of any non- Ampower Inc., entity, website, or service to which the Site links or that links to the Site.

**Modifications**

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the privacy policy periodically to stay informed about our practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

**Information we collect:**

We may store information about your use of the Service, such as the Content you post, search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Service, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, and requested and referring URLs. We may use IP or other public information to determine your general location. If you allow Ampower App to access your location information, we may also collect your geo location information. We may use this information to show your location to other users in our People You May Know section.

We may store the information you submit to or through the Service, as well as information we collect in connection with your use of the Service. If you registered/updated your profile on Ampower, we may store and use your full name, email address, city, state, country, title, company you are currently working with and other information you may provide with your registration/profile, such as your gender and birth date as well as any photo you submit through the registration process/update profile page will be publicly

The information that you post to the Site is intended for public consumption, including your reviews, comments, agree/disagree actions, pictures, comments, friend lists and account profile. We may display this information on the Service and further distribute it to a wider audience through third party sites and services. This information is totally public and anyone can view it, this information can show up on Ampower, on other search engines, and on 3

You can invite your friends to join the Service/write you a review by providing their contact information or by allowing us to use your address book from your computer, mobile device, or other sites. If you invite a friend to write a review/join/ connect with you on the Service, we may transmit your friend?s contact information to Ampower and display your friends on the People You May Know section or other sections of the Site.

**Information others share about you**

Your Friends and other people may store and share information/content about you and others that they have, such as when they upload and manage their invites and contacts. This information/content includes information such as when they write you a review, when they write a comment pertaining to you and any content they generate regarding you.

All information/content posted by your friends and other people, pertaining to you, may be displayed publicly by Ampower. This information/content may be displayed on your newsfeed, your public profile, to other people, via email, via notifications, via sms and on 3<sup>rd</sup> party sites. The exception to this is; content that is posted by your friends and other people that is marked as private-anonymous. Private anonymous content is displayed only to you. 

Please also note that the messages you send or receive as private anonymous are only private to the extent that both you and the sender/recipient keep them private. For example, we do not have any control over whether a recipient of one of your messages publicly posts it or its contents. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the anonymity of the sender of the messages submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission/storage over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we use commercially reasonable means to protect your private anonymous information we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Email Communication**

When you sign up for an account, you are by default opting in to receive emails from other Ampower users, companies, institutions, service providers and Ampower itself. You can opt-out of getting emails from Ampower here.

**Push Notifications and Alerts**

With your consent, we may send push notifications or alerts to your mobile device. You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your mobile device.

**Cookies**

We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, and similar technology in connection with your use of the Site and third party websites ("Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Service, such as your browser type, search preferences, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels"). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Service or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon. It may be possible to disable some (but not all) Cookies through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the Site. The method for disabling cookies varies by device and browser type and can usually be found in preferences or security settings.

You may terminate your account at any time by closing your account. You are free to edit or delete Your Content before closing the account. Upon closing your account you will no longer have access to edit or delete Your Content. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a period of time.

**Analytics Services Provided by Others**

We may allow third parties to provide analytics services to us. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Service, including your IP address, reviews you wrote, reviews you viewed, agree/disagree data, comments time spent on reviews, and conversion information. This information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity.

**Investigations**

We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure is (a) reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process lawfully served on us; (b) helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site; or (c) protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public.

**Links:**

The Site may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

**Children**

The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to anyone under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us here. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information we will take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

**Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security

**Jurisdiction**

The information we obtain from or about you may be processed and stored in the United States, which may provide for different data protection rules than the country in which you reside. We comply with the EU &amp; Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Frameworks as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. We will respond to requests relating to personal data within 30 days. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification, please visit http://export.gov/safeharbor.

**Dispute Resolution**

If you believe that Ampower has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may contact us online by

**Ampower**

Attn: Privacy Officer

Plot no: C-5/1, Lane 2,

Vikrampuri Colony, Secunderabad - 500009,

Telangana, INDIA.
